# 微笑辅助器
Smiling Aid Device
# 经常听说爱笑的人运气不会太差
I often hear that people who smile a lot tend to have good luck
# 但是有一些朋友由于性格精力或者一些糟糕的现状
But due to personality, past experience or bad circumstances
# 脸上很少露出笑容
Some friends rarely have smile on their face
# 总是拉着脸
Always lack of happiness
# 这样对生活和工作都有一定的影响
This has a certain impact on life and work
# 久而久之，他会形成一个死循环
Over time, it will form a vicious circle
# 为此，我为这些人群做了一个笑容辅助器
For this, I made a smiling aid device for these people
# 这个笑容辅助器前面有两个钩子
There are two hooks in the front of this device
# 使用的时候只需要把它戴到头上钩住嘴唇
When you use it, you just need to wear it around your head and hook up your lips
# 然后拧动后面的按钮
Then turn the knob in the back
# 这样他就会自然收紧
So that it naturally tightens
# 通过物理的方式让相容慢慢呈现出来
So that a smile is gradually presented via physical means
# 还可以轻松地保持一整天
You can easily keep it all day
# 下面我给大家试一下
Now let me test it for you
# 铁裤衩
Iron Pants
# 跳一跳
"Jump Jump" (WeChat Mini App Game)
# 听力辅助器
Hearing Aids
# 有时候人们为了听得更远更真一些
Sometimes when people want to hear further or clearer
# 也常常把手放在耳后来增加听力
they cup their hands around the ear to amplify sounds
# 根据这个原理 我做了一个这个东西
According to the idea, I made this thing
# 给你们试试佩戴后的效果
Let me put it on and test it for you
# 这是个... 这是个（听不清）您带上看看试试
This is... This is hearing aid, could you wear it and try?
# 就...就...就这听力，有没有改进不？
Is... Is.. Is there any improvements in hearing?
# 嗯 没有感觉
Ummm... Not quite
# （手工耿 订阅 评论 点赞！）
Handicraft Geng -- Subscribe! Comment! Like!